<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2023-07-09T03:47:18+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Mark Morowczynski&apos;s home page. Occasional blog posts, various presentations, and contact info.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">SABR, SANS and KQL</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/SABR-SANS-KQL/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SABR, SANS and KQL" /><published>2023-07-08T16:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-07-08T16:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/SABR-SANS-KQL</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/SABR-SANS-KQL/"><![CDATA[<p>I’m a bit behind schedule on blog posts. June was a hectic month, and when I finally looked up, it was over. So where did my time go if I wasn’t spent focusing on security research?</p>

<p>As the homepage says, I enjoy watching baseball, hockey, and basketball outside of technology. That’s a bit simplistic, and besides playing fantasy baseball, I’m also a member of the Society For American Baseball Research, better known as <a href="https://sabr.org/">SABR</a>. You might have heard this when you watched that Moneyball movie, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3MjxoaynCmk">“Because he gets on base.”</a> SABR was around long before that and continues long after. Though there is a significant focus on baseball stats, one of the things they do is preserve the history of the game. There are many aspects of that, but where I spent my time was on their <a href="https://sabr.org/bioproject">biography project</a>.</p>

<p>Late last year, my friend and fellow SABR member, <a href="https://www.ericconrad.com/">Eric Conrad</a>, decided we would try to write something for this project. Shortly after that, a call for volunteers went out for members to write biographies for an upcoming 2004 Boston Red Sox book. Eric is a Red Sox fan, so we raised our digital hands despite having no idea what we were doing. We were assigned Sandy and Anastacio Martinez, who is most likely NOT the Martinez you think of when you think of this Boston team. This whole writing process is a much longer story: asking people in Toronto to go to the local library, Eric buying a lot of old Sporting News off eBay, and me making an international cold call to Sandy on a Monday morning. We are really pleased with how these turned out, and we have some more SABR stuff coming that I’ll share in the future, but this took much more time than I thought it would.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/img/Moneyball.jpg" alt="Moneyball" /></p>

<p>I also enrolled in the <a href="https://www.sans.edu/cyber-security-programs/graduate-certificate-cloud-security/">SANS Cloud Security Graduate Certificate Program</a>. Much of my day-to-day work focuses on Cloud Infrastructure Entitlement Management or CIEM. I have a decent knowledge of Azure but very little of AWS and GCP. I just wrapped up the first class in the program, <a href="https://www.sans.org/cyber-security-courses/cloud-security-essentials/">Cloud Security Essentials</a>. Much time has also been spent outside of work preparing for this entire space.</p>

<p>This leads me to the final bit, Kusto Query Language, aka <a href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/data-explorer/kusto/query/">KQL</a>. For the last year, I’ve been bothering <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/matthewzorich/">Matthew Zorich</a> to write this book on KQL. My skills on KQL fall into the ‘could be better’ bucket, so I was excited to read this. A series of events have occurred, and now Matthew, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rodtrent/">Rod Trent</a>, and myself are signed up to write ‘The Definitive Guide to KQL: Using Kusto Query Language for Operations, Defending, and Threat Hunting.’ This will be out sometime in 2024. I’ll focus on the language’s fundamental aspects, but this will be an excellent forcing function for me to REALLY understand this language. Look for more updates on this later.</p>

<p>Until next time.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="notes" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do baseball, security and Kusto have in common?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Contributing to LOOBins</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/LOOBins/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Contributing to LOOBins" /><published>2023-05-29T16:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-29T16:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/LOOBins</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/LOOBins/"><![CDATA[<p>I came across this open-source project called <a href="https://www.loobins.io/">LOOBins</a> which I thought would be the perfect place to get started in doing some macOS research and provide something of value to the security community.</p>

<p>LOOBins stands for Living Off the Orchard, get it, cause of ‘Apple.’ Like many security tools, we got to have some jokes in there. It’s looking for built-in macOS binaries and how threat actors can use them for malicious purposes. This concept of ‘Living Off The Land’ isn’t new, but seeing something like this for macOS is excellent.</p>

<p>Luckily, I could pick a binary, hdiutil, and contribute to the project <a href="https://www.loobins.io/binaries/hdiutil/">here</a>. This required me to research how this worked, look to see if it had been used before in a malicious way, which it actually had, and then see where this fit in the MITRE Att&amp;ck. This took me a bit longer than I thought it would, and there are probably more scenarios I need to add, but I’m pleased it was accepted.</p>

<p>If you are interested in contributing, several other binaries are looking for someone to look at. The complete issues list can be found <a href="https://github.com/infosecB/LOOBins/issues">here</a>. I’m wrapping up a few other non-tech-related writing projects shortly, but this is a project I hope to be able to continue to contribute to in the future.</p>

<p>I also realize it’s been about a month since my last post. So I’ll try to post a bit more frequently going forward but at least post once a month.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="research" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Living Off the Orchard, macOS Binaries]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I’m Learning Objective-C &amp;amp; Other Learning Resources</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/Why-ObjectiveC/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I’m Learning Objective-C &amp;amp; Other Learning Resources" /><published>2023-04-23T14:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-23T14:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/Why-ObjectiveC</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/Why-ObjectiveC/"><![CDATA[<p>‘Why are you learning Objective-C? Everything is moving to Swift.” This is usually the first thing someone will helpfully point out to me. They are not wrong either. If you were getting started in the iOS/iPadOS ecosystem, you would probably want to use Swift.</p>

<p>When I look at Swift code somewhere, I have a rough idea of what it’s trying to do. However, when I look at the Objective-C code, it looks like the cat walked across the keyboard when I was getting coffee.</p>

<p>I’m looking to learn it for a few reasons.</p>

<ol>
  <li>
    <p>Though Swift is the new and the right direction. There is still ALOT of stuff written in Objective-C, especially malware. To understand what it’s doing, you need to know Objective-C.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Trying to learn some of the deeper parts of the system requires you to use a lower-level language like C, C++, or Objective-C. I am writing small sample apps. Reversing them to see what it looks like in various tools like Ghidra, IDA Pro (which I do not have), or Hopper (which I also do not have but isn’t too expensive). Making those mistakes that other vulnerable apps make in my sample apps will help me learn. At least, I think it will.</p>
  </li>
</ol>

<p>I can also learn Swift later, it’s not like it’s going away, and you can only pick one. So I will just learn more about it later.</p>

<p>I have a terrible habit of buying books I do not have the time to read, but I do it anyways. This extends to digital, audio, and physical books. This habit includes technical books as well. I plan to use the following books for my deeper understanding of things.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.informit.com/store/objective-c-programming-the-big-nerd-ranch-guide-9780321942067">Objective-C Programming from Big Nerd Ranch</a></p>

<p>This is ten years old at this point, so some of the examples in XCode have been moved or removed, but the fundamentals are still there. You can probably find it used as well cause who would want to learn this today with all that sweet Swift stuff out there. They have a little challenge to do at the end of each chapter. I’ve been doing those as I go and posting my solutions on my <a href="https://github.com/MarkMorow/BigNerdRanchObjectiveC">GitHub Repo</a>. I’m halfway through the book, and it’s been really helpful.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.wiley.com/en-us/The+Mac+Hacker%27s+Handbook-p-9781118080337">The Mac Hackers Handbook</a></p>

<p>Another old one but many of the fundamentals remain true. For example, understanding universal binaries, tracing, and fuzzing will still work today. It might be a different toolset now, but the basics are here. I’ve learned that having a good grasp on those fundamental/basic things makes learning the newer things much easier since they are all built from them.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.wiley.com/en-us/Blue+Fox%3A+Arm+Assembly+Internals+and+Reverse+Engineering-p-9781119746720">ARM Assembly Internals &amp; Reverse Engineering</a></p>

<p>This book just arrived this past week, and I’m very excited to dig into this one. I’ve been waiting for Maria Markstedter (<a href="https://twitter.com/Fox0x01">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://mastodon.social/@Azeria">Mastodon</a>) since she announced it. The last chapter applies the techniques in the book to MacOS malware on ARM. It looks great.</p>

<p>I have a bunch more books sitting on my shelf to dig into, but those will be for another post.</p>

<p>What are some of the technical books you are either working through or most excited to start on? Please post them in the comments. I’m still not sure I set that up correctly.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="notes" /><category term="code" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't you know about Swift?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hello World!</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/hello-world/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World!" /><published>2023-04-13T15:59:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-13T15:59:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/hello-world/"><![CDATA[<p>It’s a rule all technical blogs start with this post. You can read the home page for a bit more <a href="/">about me</a>, which I’ll keep up to date.</p>

<p>But just getting this up and running has helped me improve my Git, GitHub, and Markdown skills. You’ll know they’ve really improved when I don’t have to make several other pull requests to fix mistakes here.</p>

<p>Now that the easy part is done, anyone can start a site with a blog; the real trick is keeping it going. I hope to post, at a minimum, what I’m learning.</p>

<p>For things related to Azure AD, you can and should read the official blog for <a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/bg-p/Identity">Azure AD posts</a>.</p>

<p>Please leave a comment on what you are learning (this will help me make sure comments are actually working)!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="notes" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saying hello to everyone out there]]></summary></entry></feed>