<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2024-05-26T23:08:33+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Mark Morowczynski&apos;s home page. Occasional blog posts, various presentations, and contact info.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The Definitive Guide to KQL Now Available</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/KQL-Is-Available/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Definitive Guide to KQL Now Available" /><published>2024-05-26T16:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-26T16:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/KQL-Is-Available</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/KQL-Is-Available/"><![CDATA[<p>The wait is over! After 10 months from start to finish, you can now purchase The Definitive Guide to KQL: Using Kusto Query Language for operations, defending, and threat hunting. This comprehensive guide covers everything from the basics of KQL to advanced techniques for threat hunting and defense. The Microsoft Press <a href="https://www.microsoftpressstore.com/store/definitive-guide-to-kql-using-kusto-query-language-9780138293383">store</a> or <a href="https://a.co/d/d2DZKaF">Amazon</a> I suspect will be the most common places of purchase.</p>

<p>My author copies arrived this week, and the quote often attributed to Dorothy Parker, “I hate to write, but I love having written,” applies. There is no evidence she ever said that, but the feeling rings true.</p>

<p>This book is the book I wish existed when I was starting to learn KQL. Writing it made me dig deeper into the language to examine some of the things ‘you just do’. My co-authors, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rodtrent/">Rod Trent</a> and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/matthewzorich/">Matthew Zorich</a>, are incredibly knowledgeable, and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/corissakoopmans/">Corissa Koopmans</a>, the technical reviewer, went above and beyond with the book.</p>

<p>We tried to make the book as real-world and practical as possible. I’m really happy with how it turned out. If you find it useful, please let us know.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/img/KQL.png" alt="KQL" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="code" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shipping now!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SANS SEC488 Cloud Security Essentials</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/SANS-SEC-488/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SANS SEC488 Cloud Security Essentials" /><published>2024-02-18T16:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-02-18T16:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/SANS-SEC-488</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/SANS-SEC-488/"><![CDATA[<p>In the spring of 2023, I signed up for the SANS graduate certificate program for <a href="https://www.sans.edu/cyber-security-programs/graduate-certificate-cloud-security/">cloud security</a>. I’m no stranger to SANS courses, completing their master’s program from 2018 through 2022. Luckily, my employer has a tuition reimbursement program allows me to take these courses over multiple years to maximize the benefit. It was a lot of work, but I learned a lot in each SANS course. The community I’ve met throughout my time has also been fantastic. If you can afford it, I highly recommend SANS.</p>

<p>Before enrolling in this course, explain why I signed up for four other courses. Living in the Microsoft identity world, I am familiar with Azure. I’ve taken several Azure exams and have a general idea of the correct direction. When it comes to Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Google Cloud Platform (GCP), I have never even touched it. I’m aware of some of the very basics, such as storage in AWS being called S3, GCP having virtual machines, etc. But I needed to familiarize myself with how you set this up and what the best practices are.</p>

<p>I was also starting to spend more time at work with <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/security/business/identity-access/microsoft-entra-permissions-management">Microsoft Entra Permissions Management (MEPM)</a>, a cloud infrastructure entitlement management (CIEM) product. This is integrated with AWS and GCP, as well as Azure. Going deeper on AWS and GCP would be a big help on many of the findings and remediation actions MEPM recommends, which requires some knowledge of these additional cloud providers. Finally, most customers I work with are in at least two of these clouds. There are further courses that I also had weak spots in that I needed to improve on, so I signed up for the program.</p>

<p>The first course in their program is <a href="https://www.sans.org/cyber-security-courses/cloud-security-essentials/">Security 488: Cloud Security Essentials</a>. You can read the site for all the full details of what’s covered, but at a high level, you create your own AWS account and Azure subscription, along with the IAM accounts to go with it. You then spin up a small Linux VM in Azure and set up your lab environment for the week via Terraform. You don’t have to write terraform code, but it spins up this really nice lab environment. The labs showcase the different topics covered and give some nice things to go back to and ensure you are doing in your own environment.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/img/CDCALab.png" alt="Lab" />
<em>The SEC 488 lab diagram that you use throughout the five day course.</em></p>

<p>Then, throughout the five days, you’ll cover the fundamentals of each cloud provider as you build out the environment for a fictional rock band CD/CA. When teaching a topic, take networking, for example; it will start with the basics and use AWS as the first example. Then, it will move to Azure and call out where it’s different. Finally, the topic will move to GCP. This style tends to make the course content skew a bit heavier to AWS, then Azure, and finally, GCP is the smallest. This is aligned with what I see at most customers where AWS and Azure are the vast majority, and there is possibly some GCP for specific workloads. If you are a very large GCP shop, consider looking at something more specific to that elsewhere.</p>

<p>For me, this course was a really great introduction to the other additional cloud providers. This is a 400-level fundamental course, so there wasn’t anything too tricky topic-wise. Many of the topics were covered in other security courses, but this had the cloud flavor of it. I’d recommend this course if you are getting started in this cloud space or are really heavy on one cloud provider and beginning to branch out. This would also be great as a second course if you have just taken SEC 401 Security Essentials and then wanted to get started with the cloud. If you’ve been maintaining two or three of these cloud providers for several years, have made a few mistakes along the way, and learned from them, you probably won’t find as much value as I did.</p>

<p>The GIAC <a href="https://www.giac.org/certifications/cloud-security-essentials-gcld/">Cloud Security Essentials (GCLD)</a> exam is pretty straightforward, like most GIAC exams. I will give you a tip in making your index that I did. Put the topic area first and then add the cloud provider next if you need to. This prevents you from remembering whether you called something Amazon AWS or AWS or a feature like CloudTrail. This will help you locate the area quicker when taking the exam.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="notes" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[GIAC GCLD Exam]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SANS SEC510 Public Cloud Security AWS, Azure and GCP</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/SANS-SEC-510/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SANS SEC510 Public Cloud Security AWS, Azure and GCP" /><published>2024-02-18T16:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-02-18T16:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/SANS-SEC-510</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/SANS-SEC-510/"><![CDATA[<p>As discussed in my previous <a href="https://markmorow.com/blog/2024/SANS-SEC-488/">post</a>, I took SEC 510 shortly after taking 488. This class is an excellent extension to that. You can read all the class specifics at the <a href="https://www.sans.org/cyber-security-courses/public-cloud-security-aws-azure-gcp/">site</a>. Where 488 covered these cloud concepts and set up an environment using Terraform, 510 actually goes deeper, where you discuss what it takes to set up a cloud environment and create and modify similar Terraform scripts. If you are tasked with setting up your organization’s cloud infrastructure and being able to do so by focusing on automation and security across all three cloud providers, 510 is a great class.</p>

<p>In 510 there is a similar fake company you are working at the pre-work setup requires you to create an AWS account, Azure subscription and a GCP project. You can pick which cloud you want to use for most of the labs or do the same lab in all three clouds. This is really great and showcases what it takes to run an application or service in multiple clouds. I started doing each lab in all three but eventually ended up just rotating through to get good exposure in all of them.</p>

<p>As for the GIAC GPCS exam, it was similar to the practice tests and again straightforward. Something that helped me a lot was making sure I could easily pull up any of the slides with the Terraform configuration. I scored very well on this exam and felt I could have dug deeper into the Terraform aspects. If I were in a cloud engineering-type role rolling out cloud infrastructure, I would refer back to this and do some of the optional labs.</p>

<p>Overall, this was a really great course!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="notes" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[GIAC GPCS Exam]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Mac Hacker’s Handbook</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/2024-The-Mac-Hackers-Handbook/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Mac Hacker’s Handbook" /><published>2024-01-27T16:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-27T16:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/2024-The-Mac-Hackers-Handbook</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/2024-The-Mac-Hackers-Handbook/"><![CDATA[<p>In 2011, Wiley released <a href="https://www.wiley.com/en-us/The+Mac+Hacker%27s+Handbook-p-9781118080337">The Mac Hacker’s Handbook</a> by Charlie Millerwon and Dino Dai Zovi. The book focuses on the basics of Mac OS X (note this is before it was called OS X and now just macOS), the attack surface of the operating system, looking for bugs and vulnerabilities, as well as many of the tools and techniques you would use to exploit it. This is similar in style to the many other The ‘insert name’ hacker’s handbook, with ‘Web Application’ being the one I see recommended the most. This book leverages Mac OS X 10.5, also known as Leopard, as the host operating system to walk through teaching you these different attacks and tools.</p>

<p>You might wonder, Mac OS X 10.5, do those attacks still work? They do not. We are talking about an operating system that was released in 2007. The first Apple computer I bought was an iBook G4 that came with Mac OS X 10.4 Tiger, and I remember upgrading it to Leopard and eventually Snow Leopard. Yes, it is old. So why do this? First, you’d be surprised at how many of the tools you’ll still use today that are covered in this book. Second, these techniques are fundamental and much easier to do on this older operating system. This is a great way to learn and apply it to much more modern and better-protected operating systems. You have to crawl before you can run.</p>

<p>This brings us to the next challenge: how do you run Mac OS X 10.5 in 2024. I do not have my iBook G4 anymore. My first step was to try to run this as a virtual machine on VMWare Fusion. I ran into two challenges. First, in order to install, you need to take the DMG file and convert it to an ISO. The good news is that the built-in Disk Utility tool can convert a DMG to an ISO. The second issue was that VMWare Fusion would only run MacOS X Server licenses as per its license agreement. I did not have a copy of Mac OS X Leopard Server, and I suspect many of the examples in the book would work, but I wasn’t sure.</p>

<p>I then tried installing Mac OS X 10.5 in Virtual Box, and I got a bit further along as it actually started. I was met with a kernel panic: “com.apple.driver.AppleIntelCPUPowerManagement”. Doing a bit of searching led me to a similar post <a href="https://forums.virtualbox.org/viewtopic.php?t=109476">here</a>. The fix is to set the virtual CPU with this command, /Applications/VirtualBox.app/Contents/MacOS/VBoxManage modifyvm Leopard –cpu-profile ‘Intel Core2 T7600 2.33GHz’. Leopard is the name of my VM.</p>

<p>After that, it booted and installed as expected! I now have my test environment set up and ready to go!</p>

<p><img src="/assets/img/Leopard_Running_VirtualBox.png" alt="Leopard" />
<em>Mac OS X 10.5 Leopard running in a VM in Virtual Box on Macbook Pro host</em></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="research" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Isn't that book really old?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2024 Update</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/2024_Update/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2024 Update" /><published>2024-01-07T16:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-07T16:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/2024_Update</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2024/2024_Update/"><![CDATA[<p>Sorry, it has been so long. Let’s start with the good news first. The KQL book is nearly done. I say nearly because it’s not done done. It’s still going through the copy editor phases, and I’ll need to do a final review and edits. This is minor, though, compared to the core writing. We contacted numerous Microsoft folks to get some of their favorite and recommended KQL queries. The book is already up on Amazon for <a href="https://a.co/d/cHevMAX">purchase</a>.</p>

<p>The bad news is that this took much of the free time I had planned to write things here. I also finished an additional SANS cloud security class, <a href="https://www.sans.org/cyber-security-courses/public-cloud-security-aws-azure-gcp/">SEC 510 Public Cloud Security: AWS, Azure, and GCP</a>, and I’m nearly done with <a href="https://www.sans.org/cyber-security-courses/cloud-security-attacker-techniques-monitoring-threat-detection/">SEC 541 Cloud Security Attacker Techniques, Monitoring, and Threat Detection</a>. I’ll write up some little reviews of those as well.</p>

<p>I have also taken on another <a href="https://sabr.org/">SABR</a> project around the 2005 White Sox, but that’s a story for another post. But with the turn of the calendar, I have several other posts I’m working on and hope to post more frequently; it really can’t get any more less frequent.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="notes" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What have you been doing all this time?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SABR, SANS and KQL</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/SABR-SANS-KQL/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SABR, SANS and KQL" /><published>2023-07-08T16:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-07-08T16:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/SABR-SANS-KQL</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/SABR-SANS-KQL/"><![CDATA[<p>I’m a bit behind schedule on blog posts. June was a hectic month, and when I finally looked up, it was over. So where did my time go if I wasn’t spent focusing on security research?</p>

<p>As the homepage says, I enjoy watching baseball, hockey, and basketball outside of technology. That’s a bit simplistic, and besides playing fantasy baseball, I’m also a member of the Society For American Baseball Research, better known as <a href="https://sabr.org/">SABR</a>. You might have heard this when you watched that Moneyball movie, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3MjxoaynCmk">“Because he gets on base.”</a> SABR was around long before that and continues long after. Though there is a significant focus on baseball stats, one of the things they do is preserve the history of the game. There are many aspects of that, but where I spent my time was on their <a href="https://sabr.org/bioproject">biography project</a>.</p>

<p>Late last year, my friend and fellow SABR member, <a href="https://www.ericconrad.com/">Eric Conrad</a>, decided we would try to write something for this project. Shortly after that, a call for volunteers went out for members to write biographies for an upcoming 2004 Boston Red Sox book. Eric is a Red Sox fan, so we raised our digital hands despite having no idea what we were doing. We were assigned Sandy and Anastacio Martinez, who is most likely NOT the Martinez you think of when you think of this Boston team. This whole writing process is a much longer story: asking people in Toronto to go to the local library, Eric buying a lot of old Sporting News off eBay, and me making an international cold call to Sandy on a Monday morning. We are really pleased with how these turned out, and we have some more SABR stuff coming that I’ll share in the future, but this took much more time than I thought it would.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/img/Moneyball.jpg" alt="Moneyball" /></p>

<p>I also enrolled in the <a href="https://www.sans.edu/cyber-security-programs/graduate-certificate-cloud-security/">SANS Cloud Security Graduate Certificate Program</a>. Much of my day-to-day work focuses on Cloud Infrastructure Entitlement Management or CIEM. I have a decent knowledge of Azure but very little of AWS and GCP. I just wrapped up the first class in the program, <a href="https://www.sans.org/cyber-security-courses/cloud-security-essentials/">Cloud Security Essentials</a>. Much time has also been spent outside of work preparing for this entire space.</p>

<p>This leads me to the final bit, Kusto Query Language, aka <a href="https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/data-explorer/kusto/query/">KQL</a>. For the last year, I’ve been bothering <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/matthewzorich/">Matthew Zorich</a> to write this book on KQL. My skills on KQL fall into the ‘could be better’ bucket, so I was excited to read this. A series of events have occurred, and now Matthew, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rodtrent/">Rod Trent</a>, and myself are signed up to write ‘The Definitive Guide to KQL: Using Kusto Query Language for Operations, Defending, and Threat Hunting.’ This will be out sometime in 2024. I’ll focus on the language’s fundamental aspects, but this will be an excellent forcing function for me to REALLY understand this language. Look for more updates on this later.</p>

<p>Until next time.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="notes" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do baseball, security and Kusto have in common?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Contributing to LOOBins</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/LOOBins/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Contributing to LOOBins" /><published>2023-05-29T16:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-29T16:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/LOOBins</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/LOOBins/"><![CDATA[<p>I came across this open-source project called <a href="https://www.loobins.io/">LOOBins</a> which I thought would be the perfect place to get started in doing some macOS research and provide something of value to the security community.</p>

<p>LOOBins stands for Living Off the Orchard, get it, cause of ‘Apple.’ Like many security tools, we got to have some jokes in there. It’s looking for built-in macOS binaries and how threat actors can use them for malicious purposes. This concept of ‘Living Off The Land’ isn’t new, but seeing something like this for macOS is excellent.</p>

<p>Luckily, I could pick a binary, hdiutil, and contribute to the project <a href="https://www.loobins.io/binaries/hdiutil/">here</a>. This required me to research how this worked, look to see if it had been used before in a malicious way, which it actually had, and then see where this fit in the MITRE Att&amp;ck. This took me a bit longer than I thought it would, and there are probably more scenarios I need to add, but I’m pleased it was accepted.</p>

<p>If you are interested in contributing, several other binaries are looking for someone to look at. The complete issues list can be found <a href="https://github.com/infosecB/LOOBins/issues">here</a>. I’m wrapping up a few other non-tech-related writing projects shortly, but this is a project I hope to be able to continue to contribute to in the future.</p>

<p>I also realize it’s been about a month since my last post. So I’ll try to post a bit more frequently going forward but at least post once a month.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="research" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Living Off the Orchard, macOS Binaries]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I’m Learning Objective-C &amp;amp; Other Learning Resources</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/Why-ObjectiveC/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I’m Learning Objective-C &amp;amp; Other Learning Resources" /><published>2023-04-23T14:19:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-23T14:19:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/Why-ObjectiveC</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/Why-ObjectiveC/"><![CDATA[<p>‘Why are you learning Objective-C? Everything is moving to Swift.” This is usually the first thing someone will helpfully point out to me. They are not wrong either. If you were getting started in the iOS/iPadOS ecosystem, you would probably want to use Swift.</p>

<p>When I look at Swift code somewhere, I have a rough idea of what it’s trying to do. However, when I look at the Objective-C code, it looks like the cat walked across the keyboard when I was getting coffee.</p>

<p>I’m looking to learn it for a few reasons.</p>

<ol>
  <li>
    <p>Though Swift is the new and the right direction. There is still ALOT of stuff written in Objective-C, especially malware. To understand what it’s doing, you need to know Objective-C.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Trying to learn some of the deeper parts of the system requires you to use a lower-level language like C, C++, or Objective-C. I am writing small sample apps. Reversing them to see what it looks like in various tools like Ghidra, IDA Pro (which I do not have), or Hopper (which I also do not have but isn’t too expensive). Making those mistakes that other vulnerable apps make in my sample apps will help me learn. At least, I think it will.</p>
  </li>
</ol>

<p>I can also learn Swift later, it’s not like it’s going away, and you can only pick one. So I will just learn more about it later.</p>

<p>I have a terrible habit of buying books I do not have the time to read, but I do it anyways. This extends to digital, audio, and physical books. This habit includes technical books as well. I plan to use the following books for my deeper understanding of things.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.informit.com/store/objective-c-programming-the-big-nerd-ranch-guide-9780321942067">Objective-C Programming from Big Nerd Ranch</a></p>

<p>This is ten years old at this point, so some of the examples in XCode have been moved or removed, but the fundamentals are still there. You can probably find it used as well cause who would want to learn this today with all that sweet Swift stuff out there. They have a little challenge to do at the end of each chapter. I’ve been doing those as I go and posting my solutions on my <a href="https://github.com/MarkMorow/BigNerdRanchObjectiveC">GitHub Repo</a>. I’m halfway through the book, and it’s been really helpful.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.wiley.com/en-us/The+Mac+Hacker%27s+Handbook-p-9781118080337">The Mac Hackers Handbook</a></p>

<p>Another old one but many of the fundamentals remain true. For example, understanding universal binaries, tracing, and fuzzing will still work today. It might be a different toolset now, but the basics are here. I’ve learned that having a good grasp on those fundamental/basic things makes learning the newer things much easier since they are all built from them.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.wiley.com/en-us/Blue+Fox%3A+Arm+Assembly+Internals+and+Reverse+Engineering-p-9781119746720">ARM Assembly Internals &amp; Reverse Engineering</a></p>

<p>This book just arrived this past week, and I’m very excited to dig into this one. I’ve been waiting for Maria Markstedter (<a href="https://twitter.com/Fox0x01">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://mastodon.social/@Azeria">Mastodon</a>) since she announced it. The last chapter applies the techniques in the book to MacOS malware on ARM. It looks great.</p>

<p>I have a bunch more books sitting on my shelf to dig into, but those will be for another post.</p>

<p>What are some of the technical books you are either working through or most excited to start on? Please post them in the comments. I’m still not sure I set that up correctly.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="notes" /><category term="code" /><category term="learning" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't you know about Swift?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hello World!</title><link href="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/hello-world/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World!" /><published>2023-04-13T15:59:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-04-13T15:59:00+00:00</updated><id>https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://wwww.markmorow.com/blog/2023/hello-world/"><![CDATA[<p>It’s a rule all technical blogs start with this post. You can read the home page for a bit more <a href="/">about me</a>, which I’ll keep up to date.</p>

<p>But just getting this up and running has helped me improve my Git, GitHub, and Markdown skills. You’ll know they’ve really improved when I don’t have to make several other pull requests to fix mistakes here.</p>

<p>Now that the easy part is done, anyone can start a site with a blog; the real trick is keeping it going. I hope to post, at a minimum, what I’m learning.</p>

<p>For things related to Azure AD, you can and should read the official blog for <a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/bg-p/Identity">Azure AD posts</a>.</p>

<p>Please leave a comment on what you are learning (this will help me make sure comments are actually working)!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="notes" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saying hello to everyone out there]]></summary></entry></feed>